http://www.hhgregg.com/pages/privacy-security

Newsletter
Please Subscribe to receive Product Launch offers & Coupon for your purchase!
Privacy
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for hhgregg.com.  This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site.  It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you.  We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us.  We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
We may change this privacy policy at any time by posting revisions through this website.
*Please be advised that orders may take 1-2 business days for processing before shipping.*
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time.  You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Text Marketing and notifications:By entering your phone number in the checkout and initialising a purchase, subscribing via our subscription form or a keyword, you agree that we may send you text notifications (for your order, including abandoned cart reminders) and text marketing offers. Text marketing messages will not exceed 5 a month. You acknowledge that consent is not a condition for any purchase.If you wish to unsubscribe from receiving text marketing messages and notifications reply with STOP to any mobile message sent from us or use the unsubscribe link we provided you with in any of our messages. You understand and agree that alternative methods of opting out, such as using alternative words or requests will not be accounted as a reasonable means of opting out. Message and data rates may apply.For any questions please text HELP to the number you received the messages from. You can also contact us for more information. If you wish to opt out please follow the procedures above.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information.  When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way.  You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information.  The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Privacy Questions
If you have any questions or concerns about hhgregg privacy policies or data processing, please contact us by emailing customercare@hhgregg.com.hhgregg may update its privacy policy from time to time. When we change the policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated privacy policy.
Subscribe to our Newsletter
Please subscribe to receive Product Launch offers & Coupon for your purchase!
100% free, Unsubscribe any time!
Free delivery sitewide
Choose from our wide range of collection
Satisfied or refunded
For any reason, you are not entirely satisfied with your purchase, we are here to help you*
Top-notch support
We ensuring to build a  genuine relationship with our users.
Secure payments
We have safer, faster, more secure way to pay online
